Guide to the Horizons Theater Company records, 1972-2015 MS2371
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative materials, 1977-2014; 1984-2002; MS2371 Series 1; 8.5 Linear Feet
  - Committee to promote Wash/notes, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Women Playwrights, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Spectrum Map, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Facts Sheet, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Administrative - Envelopes, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Box Office - Volunt Info, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Equipment Resources, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - PR Intern, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Job Descriptions, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Horizons History, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Job Description Interns, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Horizons Statement of Purpose, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Horizons - Leslie Jacobson information, undated; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Administrative Binder [1/3], 1979, 1984, 1986, 2001-2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Binder [2/3], 1979, 1984, 1986, 2001-2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Binder [3/3], 1979, 1984, 1986, 2001-2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Copies of Pro Femina/Horizons name change documents, 1984; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Administrative materials, 1988-1989, 1991-1992, 1994, 2005-2006, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Horizons History - Newsletters and Readings (to send out), 1990, 1997, 1999; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Conventions--ECTC and ATHE, 1990-1991; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Letters for Me/Annual Reports etc. [KC/ACTF Forms and other Program materials], 1992-1993, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum/"An Evening of Remembrance", 1992 November 14; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Meet the Composer [Residency Program in conjunction with Horizons], 1993; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission, 1993, 2004-2010; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Donation and contract documents, 1994, 1998-1999, 2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Development '97 [Grant and funding information], 1996-1997; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Address lists for Bravo Events/League of Washington Theatres documents, 1997, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Grant opportunities, 1997, 1999, 2006; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Horizons-Job Descriptions, 1997-1999; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous administrative and financial documents, and production-related materials, 1997-1998, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Grant information [1/3], 1997, 2001-2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Grant information [2/3], 1997, 2001-2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Grant information [3/3], 1997, 2001-2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Long Range Plan, 1998 July 14; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Horizons-5 Yr. Plan July, 1998, 1998-2000, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 1999-2000 Grants, 1998-2000, 2002-2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Grant information [1/3], 1998-2002, 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - [Grant information] MARPAT Grant/Horizons May '02 [2/3], 1998-2002, 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - [Grant information] Horizons-Grants [3/3], 1998-2002, 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Endowment of the Arts & Humanities, 1998, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Robert Prosky and his rare wood pens, 1998, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Horizons Grant Application for Gannett, 1999 December 21; MS2371 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - United Way Application, 1999; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors/Artistic Associates, 1999-2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Kenmore Evaluation 2000 [Kenmore Summer Arts & Technology Institute], 1999-2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Washington Council of Agencies [Washington Forest Foundation], 1999-2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Horizons-Grant Materials, 1999-2000, 2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Organizational Assessments, 1999, 2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Budgets [Grant proposals and information], 1999-2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Arl County Grant 2000-2001, 1999-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Bridge Builders Fund, 1999-2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - The Bridge Builders Fund Third Annual Awards Ceremony, 2000 October 11; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - "Corporate & Cultural Partnerships, Horizons Theatre", 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - CWI Clearinghouse on Women's Issues, 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Horizons Theatre website, 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Julie Taymor/National Museum of Women in the Arts, 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Source [Source Theatre Company], 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - United Way/Combined Federal Campaign Application, 2000; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Arl County Grant 2000-2001 (Materials/Sources), 2000-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Arlington Cultural Affairs Proposals '02, 2000-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Builders Fund Proposals, 2001 May 10; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Builders Grant '01, 1984-2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Tom Lane Grant, 2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - "Women's Rising Star: An Oral History of Women's Theatre in the Women's Liberation Movement", 2001; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - "An Eye on the 'Horizon' A Case Study of the Country's Longest Running Women's Theatre"/An Interview with Leslie Jacobson, 2001-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Arlington County Grant Information, 2001-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Board Minutes 2001-02, 2001-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Daily Business, 2001-2002, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - League of Washington Theatres 2001 Mena [?], 2001-2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Arlington Co. Grant Info. 2003, 2001-2003; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Tom Lane Fund, 2001, 2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - United Arts Organization of Greater Washington/United Way, 2001-2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - NEA Grant-related materials, 2001-2005; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Annual Appeal 2002, 2001, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Count Basil, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Grants, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy Center Prelude Festival 2002, MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Losing Lawrence, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Losing Lawrence, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Losing Lawrence, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Losing Lawrence Program Master, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - South African AIDS Awareness Theatre Program, 2002; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Unitarian Church Grant '03, 2002-2003; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Office Lease 9/03, 2003 September; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Open Meadows [Grant Application], 2002-2003, 2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Basil in NY [Count Basil performance at Fordham University], 2003; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Horizons-Theatre mission, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Surveys [and email correspondence], 2003-2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Ben & Jerry [Ben & Jerry's Foundation grant request], 2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous productions, 2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Pumping Josey, 2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Draft Budget for "Pumping Josey"/Profit and Loss October 2002-September 2003, 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Washington Forrest Foundation, 2004-2005; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Weissberg [Weissberg Foundation Grants], 2004-2008, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - "Organizational Background'/"The Body Project", 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Arl. Co. Project Grant 2005, MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - NEA [Grant-related materials], 2005; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Horizons/ANAD Fundraiser ["The Body Project"], 2005-2006; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Hostica [Horizon Theatre's website], 2005, 2007, 2010, 2012-2013; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - BP ["The Body Project" in Dc and Ithaca, NY], 2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 2006-2007; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Horizons Theatre Post Office Box, 2009, 2011-2014; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 2004 Contributions, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Cheat Sheets, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Horizons Stationary, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Horizons Theatre Narratives/Mission Statements, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Horizons Theatre Logo ideas, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Horizons Theatre website design mock-ups, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Horizons Staff and Board Retreat, and narrative, 1994 September 25, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Board-related materials, 1996-1997; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Horizons Guest Books, 1993, 2006, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Horizons Guest Books for "The Body Project", 2005, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Leslie Jacobson/GW Department of Theatre and Dance, circa 1970s-circa 1990s; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Leslie Jacobson [Early Pro Femina/ Horizons Theatre materials], 1974-1979, 1983-1986, 1993; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Academic Information related to Promotion--Leslie Jacobson, 1977, 1980-1986; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous materials re: Leslie Jacobson, 1973, 1982, 1993, 1997, 2001, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Leslie Jacobson professional materials, circa 1993; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Nancy Drew, 1990-1991, undated; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1998-2004, MS2371 Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Contracts, 2002-2003, 2003-2004; MS2371 Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Contracts, 2004-2006, MS2371 Series 1 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1976-2009; 1980-1989; MS2371 Series 2; 2 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series contain correspondence between Pro Femina/Horizons staff and subscribers, businesses, and other fans and theater supporters. The materials date from 1976 to 2009.
  - Bookings Support Letters, 1976-1984; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fan Mail, 1977-1982; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1978-2007; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: In, 1979-1986; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Allied Arts for D.C., 1980; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence from Susan Chaires (Lawyer), 1981-1984; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Mt. Vernon College Correspondence, 1982; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: In 1982, 1982-1983; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Letters, 1982-1986; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1988; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1995; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Georgetown Enterprises Ticket Sales, 1984; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Hawks, 1984; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence/Support Letters, 1984-1986; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Letters sent out for orgasmo, 1985; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Letter to buy houses during run for orgasmo, 1985; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Letters Mary Coleman, 1985-1986; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Support letters, 1985-1990; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Female Entertainer, 1986; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Peggy Conkling, 1986; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ms California, 1987; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1987; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Absent Minded Sweethearts Correspondence & Misc., 1987; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Three Postcards, 1988; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Letters, 1989; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bravo 89 letters, 1989; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Donated tickets, 1989-1990; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspon. rec'd, 1997-1998; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1994, 1997, 2005; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Arlington County Department of Parks and Recreation, 1997; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "In Good Company", 1998 July 18; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "Dear Esther", 1998; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - "Spinning Into Butter", circa 1998; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1998-1999, 2001, 2007-2008, undated; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - "Into the Woods", 2000; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Creative opportunity inquiries, 2001; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Claudia Allen - Unspoken Prayers, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Non-Horizons Theatre Productions, 2005; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Photo reproduction, 2009, undated; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - For Joan [re: Brian Lee Huynh], undated; MS2371 Series 2 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Scripts, 1974-2010; 1990-1999; MS2371 Series 3; 6.5 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series contain play scripts. The material dates from 1974-2010, with a significant number of undated scripts.
  This series is organized by type of script: Dated scripts are listed in chronological order while undated scripts are listed alphabetically. Arranged in two parts due to a later addition donated in 2019 and the subsequent processing project.
  - Script - The Amateur: Reflections of Zelda, 1974; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Nora, 1977; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Triptych, 1977; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Four, 1979; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Automatic Pilot, 1980; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Close Calls - Far Cries, 1981; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - American-Boy, 1982; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Papa's Violin, 1984; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - You Can't Go Home Again, 1985; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Eleemosynary, 1985; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Leader of the Pack, 1985; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Confidence, 1986; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Etta Jenks, 1986; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Speaking in Tongues, 1987; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Natives, The Piano & Journey to Beijing, 1987-1998; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Stick Wife & My Mother Said I Never Should, 1987-1991; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The State of Texas, 1988; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Full Circle, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Emily, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Tales of the Lost Formicans, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Three Ways Home, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cinzano, Columbine's Apartment, the Stairlanding, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Daytrips, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - St. Florence, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Angels of Power, 1988; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - House on Fire, 1989; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Phantasie, 1989; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - One, Two, Buckle My Shoe, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hope for Breakfast, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Winter Dreams, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Clean Slate, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Bravo Awards, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Ninth Step, 1990; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Still Life, 1991; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Eulah, 1991; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Strangers in their Own Land, 1993; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The Reincarnation of Jaimie Brown, 1994; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Theodora, 1994; Series 3 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - A Fruitwood Casket, 1994; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - A Small Delegation, 1995; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Dog Opera, 1995; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ride of a Lifetime, etc., 1995-1998; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Talisman Ring, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The Visible Horse & Daisy in the Dreamtime, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Necessary Targets, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Crumbs from the Table of Joy, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Sins of Sor Juana, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The Batting Cage, 1996; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Inns and Outs, 1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meditations/From the Ash, 1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Woman Spends Year on Labor, 1996; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kissing & A Lovely Home, 1996-1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Alligator Tales, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Pass It On, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Guitar Lessons: The Springhill Singing Disaster, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Left Hand Singing, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Oo-Bla-Dee, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Who are the Strangers, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Washington-Sarajevo Talks, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Martha, 1997; Series 3 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Sylvia's Real Good Advice, 1997; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Celestina, 1997; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Eleanor and Alice, 1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Dance with Me, 1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Christmas Spirit, 1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Good Will, 1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Pot Mom, 1998; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Three Roses, 1999; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Touching, Kissing, Holding Hands, 2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Learning Curves, 2000; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Boca Bellisima & Hecho en Cuba, 2001; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well, 2001; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Eugenio, 2004; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Intimations for Saxophone, 2004; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Play #3, 2005-2006; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - A...My Name is Alice, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - A...My Name Will Always Be Alice, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Abie's Irish Rose, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Albert Einstein Never Sang at the Met, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - A Mixed Marriage, undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Angry Housewives, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Apocalyptic Butterflies, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Closer and Secret of Success, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Coast of Utopia, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Country Girl, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Electra, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Framework, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Full Gallop, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - The Glass of Water, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Heaven-Mother, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Ladies in Waiting and The Stranger, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - The Last Game Show, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Lesson, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Letters Home, Undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Losing Lawrence, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Morning Star, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Morning's At Seven, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - O Wholly Night..., Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Of Mice Bugs and Women, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - One Curious April, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - One of the Few, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Pump Boys and Dinnettes, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Reckless, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Scripts - Play Unknown, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Sea Gull, Undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Sophie Treadwell, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Southern Girls, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Stepping Out, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Tomorrowland Script, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - The True Moon, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Virginia, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Vera, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Winter, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Woman in Mind, Undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mrs. California, 1986; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous plays [1/2], circa 1980s-circa 1990s; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous plays [2/2], circa 1980s-circa 1990s; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Strangers In Their Own Land, circa 1990s; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - The Wizard of Quiz, 1991 February; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Cinderella's Menfolk/Dora, circa 1991; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Trish & Son PLC, circa 1992; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - The Sacrificial King, Act 1 [1/2], 1993; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - The Sacrificial King, Act 2 [2/2], 1993; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Rhythms, with promotional materials, 1994; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Ms. Montage '96 [1/2], 1996 June 27; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Ms. Montage '96 [2/2], 1996 June 27; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Dear Esther, 1997; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - I Want to Tell You, 2002 September 29; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins from FATLAND / The Crossing Guard, 2004; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Pumping Josey: Life and Death in Suburbia, 2004; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins from FATLAND, 2005-2006; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Scripts from Mother/Daughter Project [Mami/Mother] [1/2], 2006; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Scripts from Mother/Daughter Project [Visiting Rights] [2/2], 2006, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Censored, 2010; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - The Body Project, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - I Want to Tell You, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - I Want to Tell You, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - I Want to Tell You, with edits/notes, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Mary S., circa 1990s; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Lisa & David, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Peace and Quiet, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - SEVEN/DC Seven, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Tea, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Thin, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Tomorrowland, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Unspoken Prayers, undated; MS2371 Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Promotional materials, 1972-2015; 1980-2007; MS2371 Series 4; 8 Linear Feet